Let's actually look at an example a real life example so that we can put into practice actually use
让我们实际看一个例子，一个现实生活中的例子，以便我们可以付诸实践实际使用
some of the things we've been talking about so far in this lesson about technical descriptions.
到目前为止，我们在本课中一直在讨论的一些关于技术描述的内容。
So when you look at a notice.
因此，当您查看通知时。
Pay attention to how we mention dates.
注意我们提到日期的方式。
Also pay attention to how we mention symbols and when symbols are not read.
还要注意我们如何提及符号以及何时不阅读符号。
I'm going to read through this then we'll just quickly talk about why certain things are said and why
我将通读此文，然后我们将快速讨论为什么要说某些事情以及为什么
certain things are not said.
有些事情没有说。
All right.
好的。
So let's read through this if you can do it in your head.
因此，如果您可以在脑海中做到这一点，那么让我们通读一遍。
Just before I do it.
就在我这样做之前。
That's great from March 14th to April 18th 2013 cafe K L dot com will be under maintenance.
太好了，从 2013 年 3 月 14 日到 4 月 18 日，cafe K L dot com 将进行维护。
We apologize for any inconvenience caused those with questions can email Miss Alice Munro at K L underscore
对于给您带来的任何不便，我们深表歉意，如有疑问，请发送电子邮件至 K L underscore 的 Alice Munro 小姐
B dot t r i x dash 4 3 9 at Yahoo.
雅虎的 B dot t r i x dash 4 3 9。
Dot com dot c n or call the store at 1 4 1 9 7 5 2 7 3 8 3.
Dot com dot c n 或致电商店 1 4 1 9 7 5 2 7 3 8 3。
Please visit one of our two locations during the following store hours Monday to Friday 8 a.m. to 10
请在以下营业时间周一至周五上午 8 点至 10 点访问我们的两个地点之一
p.m. Saturday and Sunday 10 a.m. to 6 p.m..
下午周六和周日上午 10 点到下午 6 点。
OK now let's look at this.
好的，现在让我们看看这个。
I want to mention one thing I didn't say this because this is only here because my computer is putting
我想提一件事我没有说这个因为这只是因为我的电脑正在放
the rest of this email on the next line.
这封电子邮件的其余部分在下一行。
Actually if this were on one line that wouldn't be there.
实际上，如果这是在一条线上，那将不存在。
So I didn't say dash there because it's not a real it's not a real dash.
所以我没有在那里说破折号，因为它不是真实的，它不是真正的破折号。
It's something my computer my computer did.
这是我的电脑我的电脑做的事情。
All right.
好的。
Now let's start with the date.
现在让我们从日期开始。
So I said notice that this is not an M..
所以我说注意这不是M..
OK.
好的。
So sometimes dates are written just as the month instead of 0 3 just written as 3 but I added words
所以有时日期写成月份而不是 0 3 写成 3 但我添加了单词
I said from OK from March 14th.
我从 3 月 14 日开始说好的。
Well why didn't I say from March 14th 2013.
那么我为什么不说从 2013 年 3 月 14 日开始。
The reason is because I'm saying it the second time so I'm not going to say it this time from March
原因是因为我第二次说所以从三月开始我不会说这一次
14th to April 18th 2013.
2013 年 4 月 14 日至 4 月 18 日。
I could say 2013 but I am adding T H to the 18 and T H to the 14 cafe K L dot com I'm saying dot here
我可以说是 2013 年，但我将 T H 添加到 18 并将 T H 添加到 14 cafe K L dot com 我在这里说的是 dot
because it is a U R L K you are l will be under maintenance.
因为它是一个 U R L K 你是我将在维护中。
That means it's being fixed.
这意味着它正在被修复。
We apologize for any inconvenience caused.
我们对造成的任何不便表示歉意。
Again this this one here is just to basically say hey we move this to the next line.
再说一次，这里的这个基本上只是说嘿，我们把它移到下一行。
So we definitely don't need to read those.
所以我们绝对不需要阅读这些。
OK.
好的。
Those with questions can email is this is an abbreviation.
有问题的可以发邮件，这是一个缩写。
Alice Munro at now we need to say everything here every symbol because you have to actually put this
Alice Munro 现在我们需要在这里说出每个符号的所有内容，因为您必须实际输入
in K L underscore B dot t r i x.
在 K L 下划线 B 点 t r i x。
The reason I didn't say Trix is because Trix can also be spelled as T R I C K S so I'm going to say
我没有说 Trix 的原因是因为 Trix 也可以拼写为 T R I C K S 所以我要说
T R I X dash 4 3 9 T R I X dash 4 3 9 at Yahoo.
T R I X dash 4 3 9 T R I X dash 4 3 9 在雅虎。
Dot com dot C. And so we say everything here this is going to be dash instead of Hyphen because it's
Dot com dot C. 所以我们说这里的一切都是破折号而不是连字符，因为它是
in an email address.
在电子邮件地址中。
OK now what about this one.
好的，现在这个呢。
Why did I say at here.
为什么我说在这里。
Well sometimes we use this symbol.
好吧，有时我们使用这个符号。
Right.
正确的。
This is at at.
这是在。
This is the at symbol I think you know that that's very basic but because a phone number is after this
这是 at 符号，我想您知道这是非常基本的，但是因为电话号码在此之后
we can say at here we don't usually do that.
我们可以说在这里我们通常不这样做。
Usually a colon will not be set as at.
通常不会将冒号设置为 at。
It will just be a list.
它只是一个列表。
For example like this one we don't say anything here but here it's a special case.
例如像这个我们在这里什么都不说，但这里是一个特例。
We have a phone number after it so we can say at.
我们在它后面有一个电话号码，所以我们可以说在。
If you don't say it or call the store 1 4 1 9.
如果您不说或致电商店 1 4 1 9。
OK.
好的。
Notice in the phone number we don't say parentheses we don't say hyphen or dash because we don't put
请注意，在电话号码中，我们不说括号，我们不说连字符或破折号，因为我们不放
that in the phone and we don't say this during the following store hours notice that I added from Monday
在电话里，我们不会在接下来的营业时间里说这个，请注意我从星期一开始添加的
to Friday I could say between Monday and Friday from Monday to Friday.
到星期五我可以说从星期一到星期五在星期一和星期五之间。
OK here I'll say from from 8:00 a.m. to 10 p.m. but I'm not really saying from because of the colon
好的，我会说从上午 8 点到晚上 10 点。但我并不是因为冒号而说的
I'm saying beginning here to this time from 8:00 a.m. to 10:00 p.m. I don't say this Don't say that
我是说从早上 8:00 到晚上 10:00 从这里开始到现在。我不说这个 别说那个
K then I say Saturday and Sunday not from Saturday to Sunday but just Saturday and Sunday I could I
K 然后我说周六和周日不是从周六到周日，而是周六和周日我可以
suppose but usually because this is only two days I'll use and to make it simpler.
假设但通常因为这只有两天我会使用并使其更简单。
Saturday and Sunday from 10:00 a.m. to 6 p.m. or between 10:00 a.m. and 6:00 p.m. so hopefully that
周六和周日上午 10:00 至下午 6 点。或上午 10:00 至下午 6:00 之间所以希望
gives you a better feeling about how some of these symbols and how dates can actually be used in real
让您更好地了解这些符号中的一些符号以及日期如何在实际中实际使用
life situations like a notice on a Web site.
生活情境，例如网站上的通知。
OK.
好的。
There are lots of other examples but hopefully you have a better feeling about these and when you're
还有很多其他的例子，但希望你对这些有更好的感觉，当你
looking around on the Internet or you see this kind of thing notice and phone numbers email addresses.
在互联网上环顾四周，或者你看到这种事情通知和电话号码电子邮件地址。
Pay attention to how the symbols are used and try to keep in mind some of the things that we've talked
注意符号的使用方式，并尽量记住我们讨论过的一些事情
about with regards to how to use those when to say them and when not to say them.
关于如何使用那些什么时候说，什么时候不说。
OK.
好的。
Now let's go on and talk about numbers.
现在让我们继续讨论数字。